

# JUDY BACA UX / UI DESIGNER

I am a UX/UI Designer with 8 years experience in tourism & hospitality management. During this time, I developed a strong sense of empathy for others, learned to identify their pain points and seeing the world from other people perspective. My strong desire to help others that made me excel at my previous role is what pushed me to develop my career into world of UX & UI. From my experience in management, I derived my core values of fact finding before making a decision, process optimisation, value of team work & cooperation, crucial position of communication with all stakeholders and management of expectations.



bacajudyta@gmail.com



Katowice, Poland



www.iamjudybaca.com



+48 537 934 392



www.linkedin.com/in/judyta-baca-0561101ba

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Hireright, Katowice, Poland, 2020-2021 RESEARCHER

Ensuring a first class customer and candidate experience through verifying standard education, employment, and reference information as well as conducting credit, criminal and database checks in line with qualitative and quantitative performance.

JUKE GROUP Ltd, Dundee, Scotland, 2017-2020 Gallery 48 Spanish tapas restaurant & Art Gallery GENERAL / MARKETING STRATEGY MANAGER

Day to day administration of running, general HR and staff management up to 20 people, sole responsibility of ordering, purchasing and procurement, curating for art exhibitions, leading long and short term marketing campaigns over local media, social presence and managing social media channels (Facebook & Instagram).

Tinsmith, Bar and Restaurant, Dundee, Scotland, 2017-2020 RELIEF MANAGER

Business development, securing and organizing external events, overseeing daily/ weekly & monthly paperwork for production of company files and returns.

Overseeing and ensuring legal compliance in HR department as well as admin of HR files. In charge of managing social media channels (Instagram & Facebook) marketing campaigns and business online activities.

Piperdam Golf & Leisure Resort, Dundee, Scotland, 2015-2017 TEAM LEADER

Oversee all operations to ensure that restaurant and bar runs smoothly. Manage a team of up to 10 people. Train and supervise staff. Ensure adherence to food and safety regulations. Dealing with customer complaints and financial reconciliations.

Emirates, United Arab of Emirates, 2013-2015 CABIN CREW

Provided safe and secure environment on board, delivered world class customer service, resolved conflicts of different nature.

## SKILLS

Design Thinking, Competitor Analysis,
Business Requirements, User Interviews,
Card sorting & Affinity mapping,
User Personas & Stories, Task & User Flows,
IA, Wireframing, Prototyping,
Usability Testing, Visual Design,
A/B & Preference Testing, Design Systems
& Documentation, Pen & Paper,
Low-Mid-High Fidelity Mockups

### **TOOLS**

ADOBE XD HTML5
ADOBE PHOTOSHOP CSS3
ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR
ADOBE AFTER EFFECTS
ADOBE PREMIERE PRO

### **EDUCATION**

CAREERFOUNDRY, 2021
UX / UI Designer Certificate
& Frontend Development for
Designers Specialization

UDEMY, 2021 HTML5 and CSS3 Certificate

GLASGOW CLYDE COLLEGE, SCOTLAND, 2013 Higher National Diploma in Travel and Tourism

DUNDEE COLLEGE,
SCOTLAND, 2012
Higher National Certificate in
Travel and Tourism

DOUGLAS EWART HIGH SCHOOL, SCOTLAND, 2008